that basically a phone book still
drinking again because figures Thank You
Laurie advice 12 made possible by your
nomination and selection this great
honor tires truly grateful his specialty
here with Laura since we go back back in
1999 and she said a lot of here together
once every five years so we set our
calendars for your 2020 or that will be
collection all we're going else yet we
were very privileged to serve our
community together on a news program 16
years and that was to audience
collectively yesterday at that time
overall hears about 1 billion people we
had a lot of good faithful and what
viewers and as you lose warning
interviews oh thanks I will not forget
those caves information drugs you I a
jam john force meetings out news they
have you done this kind of like when
their camel said there were more Irish
here there are a client's a similar
thing with Selena and complete I suppose
a journalist of any here I was saying
that he or she wasn't items most
eventful in my case it was a career
bookended by a number of significant
international events on one hand mix it
opening the door China and on the other
Putin invading Ukraine in between them
two front-row seat to similar events all
great interest but of deep
Lynn too many of us here through myself
included that was the nature of
Cleveland siblings the Fallen sign up 40
years ago tomorrow the murder of the
church come in El Salvador the breakup
of the Soviet Union deliberation of
Eastern Europe the Lebanese civil war
the edible part 8 channel of the wars in
Iraq and Afghanistan you could go on
good week this is a city where what
happens virtually anywhere in the world
reverberates focusing my news report on
global impact lobbies advanced hashing
brother strength night recognition
newsroom from time to time when
something of note happen to the far-off
place say let it go whose back is here
you you're the uncle across the newsroom
go ask me after the keys from over there
somewhere actually I tell I'm 37 nice
like all the honorees he receive and I
suppose it's that deep affection for our
clothes out here whether adopted her
native which draws us to server those
places for be filled beer at all that's
a genuine tricks actually politic
charism early July that selfless
dedication cement and that would include
everyone in this room to answer to these
and Solomon problems not only in our own
community across the globe have you been
part of this event since its deception
and with retrospective the men and women
were two presenters and recipients in
the hall of fame award in the past sub
like made more in this country others
were immigrants who came to achieve your
America back which still calls me here
they there and my family by Chris family
chosen area causing muscle and livers
I'm sure the story my family my life's
not a one marcolin driven straight in
our ace in any of the cases who was
fleeing the purity of various isms and
its purity of communist and fascist
socialist mosques the stylist security
of Nazism Matthias the the
partisans
all those 20th century mrs. Susan breast
impressed and try to merge in the spirit
and say that's why a generation or two
removed my life and our children and our
grandchildren thank God for Magnus
precious gift and that's why I'm sick
the Liberty that for us here pieces here
is now to play troubling a hot on this
science of the opposite of Liberty
Aramis you know many respects by the
international community here come in
Eastern Europe's community but all of
our different friends and their families
from India Asia Central America's the
Middies Africa almost laces were people
still near to be free those years of
breathing freely animators me and my
family and they was very protective so
the guy who likes to possess Liberty you
might say is the sister of opportunity
and that's also part of the story of
America and so many people here in his
room it's the story of the immigration
we heard all the stories this evening in
years past this room is full of people
who cloak to the mantle of Liberty
answered also through that you drive
opportunity and sometimes Mexican story
Teufel meeting immigrants running each
other st. Clair Avenue and lots of sense
to the other he says a young how long
you been discovered that says three
houses
Cleveland has been good and welcoming
too many people seeking living and
opportunity my family and i won i'm
letting an able to repay this great debt
in some small way over the many years
that i fell out of the academic
community I'm deeply deeply grateful to
all of you this evening for something
Vikernes randhurst my wife's parents
grandparents who never ever imagined